<resources>
    <string name="app_name">20 WAYS TO EARN MONEY</string>
    <string-array name="books">

        <item>Blogging</item>
        <item>Publish book</item>
        <item>Phone Photography</item>
        <item>Udemy</item>
        <item>Ebay</item>
        <item>Amazone Associate</item>
        <item>Afflicate Marketing</item>
        <item>Kindle Ebook</item>
        <item>Whatsapp</item>
        <item>Membership Site</item>
        <item>Mobile app</item>
        <item>Email- Marketing</item>
        <item>Social Media</item>
        <item>Facebook Marketing</item>
        <item>Translation</item>
        <item>Refer &amp; Earn</item>
        <item>Domain Names</item>
        <item>Dropshipping</item>
        <item>Become an influencer</item>
        <item>Wordpress Themes </item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="publish_bbok_activity">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020You may have heard that most writers—Self-published and traditional—are starving artists who never make more than $1000 a year. I/’ll just get this out of the way right now. Writing a book is hard work. Creating a sustainable platform with several income streams is harder. But, if this were easy, everybody would be doing it. If you are an aspiring writer, or have already published and want to scale up your book business, find writing jobs, get some writing scholarships, or even write for online publications, let’s dive into how to turn your words into income (Yes, it can be done!). You write, you publish, and you build your own book business like Jenna Moreci did creating her full-time author and YouTube business where she now gets to spend her days doing what she loves. Write and publish consistently, write high-quality books people want to buy, expand your reach by publishing across multiple platforms, and stay up-to-speed on the latest marketing strategies that are working.

\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020This is the formula most successful self-published authors are using to make a living as a writer</string>
    <string name="overview">Be your own boss in 2022. Say Goodbye to your low living Life. The Top 20 Ways To earn Money like Blogging, Affiliate Marketing, Publishing Book, Phone Photography, Become an Influencer, etc.</string>
    <string name="first_page">If you are looking for ways to create multiple streams of income, here are a few ideas that might help you. How to earn passive income. Learn how to earn extra income using your existing skills, or invest in yourself to develop more. Earning extra income is possible.</string>
    <string name="dropshipping">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020As with any other business, building a successful dropshipping business takes significant commitment and a long-term perspective. If you are hoping for a six-figure income from six weeks of part-time work, you are going to be sadly disappointed. By approaching your business with realistic expectations about the investment required and your profitability, you will be much less likely to get discouraged and quit.
     \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020If you have the option to work on your business full-time, it is the best choice to improve your profit potential and chance of dropshipping success . Focusing all your efforts on marketing is especially helpful in the early days when building momentum is crucial. Based on our experience, it will usually take at least 12 months of full-time work with a strong emphasis on marketing for a dropshipping business to replace an average full-time income of $50,000.
    \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020All businesses and entrepreneurs are unique, but it is possible Dropshipping to generate  $1,000–$2,000 monthly income stream within 12 months working approximately 10 to 15 hours per week building your business.
    </string>
    <string name="domain_names"> \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020The primary advantage of domain flipping is the possible profit margins. For instance, the domain names broke records when it sold for $13 million. You can buy low and sell high from the convenience of your home office with practically no technical skills whatsoever. On the downside, all of the easy money has been made at this point. In 2012, Investing.com was the top seller at $2.45 million. Realistically, the average domain sold for profit goes for $2,000. Regardless, there’s plenty of money left to be made with the right strategy.
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020The first thing to do is research domain names that may be valuable to buyers with deep pockets. Google’s Keyword Tool for AdWords is a great place to start. Look for keywords with moderate to high traffic volumes and think of domain names that incorporate them. You can buy domain names for less than $10.. If you’d like to start actively marketing your domains, you can use Sedo to advertise. In addition, forums like DNForum and NamePros are great places to sell your property.
</string>
    <string name="refer_and_aearn">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020What is Refer and Earn? When you refer a friend and invite them to sign up with MobiKwik, both you and your friend earn money by referral code. You earn Rs 100 SuperCash each, when your friend adds Rs 50 in their wallet. You can earn up to Rs 5,000 SuperCash through Refer and Earn. Refer and earn is a great method of making some side income. You do not need to do many efforts for making money, all you need do is refer the apps to your friends or family members. The other person could be a friend or an acquaintance or maybe your colleague. It has been observed that mouth-to-mouth recommendations are one of the best ways of marketing a product, and some firms use the referral system for marketing their products to a broader audience. There are various best refer and earn apps in the market that have unique ways of rewarding referrals or encouraging people to refer their services to another.One of the most attractive features of referral marketing is that it is one of the most cost-effective methods of marketing your product and increasing brand awareness. With the right timing and the necessary software tools, you can flourish your business and along with that, you need to reward the people in the chain with a sound referral system as it can help get more business consistently.</string>
    <string name="translations">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020You can usually make $20 per 1000 words as an online translator but some jobs you can make good money on, while others are more competitive. A text that is to be translated from Swedish to another language or vice versa, you can make a pretty good profit on.
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020An hourly rate in India is not so high, as someone who lives in Sweden and writes both Indian and English will have little left to translate text.
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020However, there is good income from translations between Swedish / Norwegian, Savonian / Danish, Swedish / Finnish, and Swedish / English.
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020You can earn translation jobs for individual articles from 50 kronor to a couple of hundred kronor, while for larger projects (translation of blogs, websites, etc.) it is possible to earn 10,000 kronor or even more!
        \n\n<b>Best Ways to Earn Money from Translatations:-</b>
\n1. Translation of SEO texts
\n2. Translate websites from home
\n3. Make Money From Proofreading
\n4. Video translations
</string>
    <string name="facebook_marketing_one">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Since the Facebook Ad is an indirect medium of earning money, you first need to invest a small amount in the Ad campaign to go live and only then you will start earning out of it. The money you spend on an ad to be run for a single day is flexible and can be decided by you according to your own budget. What professionals and marketers forget is that there is a lot more efforts required than just investing the money. The ad must be designed and crafted in a way that any potential customer is easily converted into a client within no time.
        \n\n<b>Best Ways to Earn Money from Facebook Marketing:-</b>
\n1. The Image must be self- explanatory and attractive
\n2. Content of the Facebook Ad
\n3. You can use the Split test concept for the campaign, to judge its effectiveness
\n4.  Collect the contact details of your lead- Capture your leads
\n5.  Keep a track of the CTR
</string>
    <string name="social_media">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020However, these social media accounts make money online, too. All via a social marketing and sales strategy .
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020It is definitely easier to earn through social media if you have a huge following. But you shouldn’t despair if you have only a few. This article will provide you with some creative ways of making money on social media even if you have less than 1,000 followers.
        \n\n<b>Best Ways to Earn MoneyFrom Social Media:-</b>
\n1.Keep your account active
\n2.Keep up to date with current trends
\n3.Define your niche and be consistent
\n4.Affiliate marketing
\n5.Sell your own products
\n6.Market your skills
\n7. Become a social media manager
</string>
    <string name="mobile_app">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020What is everyone doing on their phones? Well, 90% of the total time spent on mobile is actually spent on apps. This is encouraging enough for anyone who owns a mobile app or wants to develop one.
        \n\n<b>Best Ways to Earn Money Making a Mobile App:-</b>
\n1. In-App Advertisements
\n2. In-App Purchases
\n3.Freemium Upsell
\n4.Sponsorship
\n5. Subscription
\n6.Crowdfunding
\n7. One-time payment

</string>
    <string name="whatsapp">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Whatsapp and its engagement matrix shows us that it has great earning potential. You cannot run ads or monetize your WhatsApp account like other social media platforms for example YouTube. According to the survey conducted by Statista there are over 487 million WhatsApp users in India. Finding out some of the best ways through which you can earn money from WhatsApp manually can be a lengthy and time-consuming process, but don’t worry we have done all the hard work for you. We have mentioned some of the best ways through which you can easily make money with WhatsApp.
        \n\n<b>Best Ways to Earn Money through whatsapp-</b>
        \n1. Start Affiliate Marketing,
\n2. Starting your own business on WhatsApp,
\n3. Viral Content
\n4. Using PPD networks
\n5. Promoting Applications
\n6. Drive Traffic to Your Blog
\n7. Refer Friends to Apps:
</string>
    <string name="phone_photography">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Due to the rapid change in technology in recent years, the smartphone camera has improved a lot. In some cases, it is competing with expensive DSLR cameras. However, we all know that DSLR has the edge over mobile cameras. But, we can still capture a very good photo in our mobile camera.
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020If you have a passion for photography and you can\'t afford a camera for it, you can start it with your smartphone. I don\'t say that for photography you don\'t need a camera but you can start with your smartphone camera. After you start earning you can definitely go for some good cameras to capture a high-quality photo.
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020For mobile photography, you obviously need a decent camera smartphone. Nowadays smartphone launching their phone with a great camera setup. You must buy a good camera phone according to your budget segment. For better camera quality you can simply buy a lens that is priced around 200-500 and it is easily available in online stores.
</string>
    <string name="become_an_influencer">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020The average influencer makes $2,970 per month. “Average” numbers aren’t the best to go by, since there’s so much differentiation between the highs and lows—as is referenced in the next stat!
 \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Average monthly income nears $3,000
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020The first key takeaway from HypeAuditor\'s report is that half of the influencers surveyed (48.5%) say they make money from their Instagram account. On average, an influencer earns $2,970 per month. However, there are significant differences in income among accounts, notably depending on the number of followers. Micro-influencers (between 1,000 and 10,000 followers) make an average $1,420 per month. Mega-influencers (more than one million followers) make $15,356 per month. Still, among holders of accounts with between 1K and 10K followers, only 22.99% report making money, compared to 68.75% of accounts with 500K to one million followers.
</string>
    <string name="wordpress_themes">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020There have been numerous development teams making money selling WordPress themes that “make close to $500K/year with around $200-$250K” in HR and technology costs.
        \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Real Estate theme category and sorted it by number of sales. The top three selling themes in this category are priced at an average of $50 and have an average of over 3,450 sales. That’s earnings of around $172,500 on just a single theme.   How much a WordPress developer can earn from making plugins or themes will depend on a lot of factors from startup budget to skill level to the level of innovation the product provides. Still, it is possible to make a good living doing this. You just have to get your ducks in a row first.        </string>
    <string name="email_marketing">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020The average email marketing specialist can make about $50,000 a year. This number varies by experience and by location, starting as low as $40,000, and going as high as $100,000, and even more in some locales. These numbers are on par with those of their digital marketing counterparts.Email marketing is essential for brands—big and small—looking to widen their audience and drive more high-quality leads to their website. But it takes time, patience, and a hunger for this competitive and ever-changing landscape in order to bring about those results.
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020A marketing team is nothing without a team of expert email marketing specialists. With them, digital marketing campaigns can transcend the expected into something extraordinary.
</string>
    <string name="facebook_marketing">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Facebook ad management means just that — managing Facebook ad campaigns for clients. A Facebook ad manager creates and executes a Facebook ad strategy that attracts new customers, leads, and traffic that they want for their business.
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020The ad manager listens to a client’s goals and creates graphics, ad copy, target audiences, and tests campaigns to try to meet those objectives at the lowest cost per conversion possible. They might also create images, sales copy, and oversee the advertising budget.

</string>
    <string name="amazon_associate">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020You can make from $100 to $25000 from an Amazon affiliate website. Not a single penny u can make if your site has poor traffic. And, you can earnmore if there\'s a big number of visitors coming to your blog. With multiple successful channels, the income canbe pushed to a higher position.                                                         You can earn, on average, from $100 to $20,000 from the Amazon Affiliate program, depending on how many referrals you generate for Amazon. The Amazon Affiliate program operates on a commission basis, meaning you’ll make a percentage per sale.
\n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020The commission rate differs depending on the product category. For instance, if you run an automotive blog, you can earn 4.50% from each sale. If you sell three car parts at $1,000 each in one day, you/’d make $135 from those three transactions. If you sell the same product 30 times per month, you/’d make $1,350 every month.
</string>
    <string name="e_bay">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020The average eBay seller earns about $35,000 per year. Some top earners make as much as $70,000, and many earn just a few thousand per year. It all depends on how much inventory you can sell, the price of your items, and any extra expenses that you incur like shipping materials. After setting up a store and putting in a little more time I was able to start bringing in over $1,000 per month on eBay (and often more), all for just an hour or two of work every couple of days!</string>
    <string name="udemy">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Udemy Business is a fast-growing, subscription-based enterprise learning solution, offering a curated selection of thousands of Udemy\’s top-rated courses to leading organizations around the world. Thousands of companies leverage Udemy Business to engage employees in learning from the freshest, highest-quality content on the market.
        \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Each month, Udemy allocates 25% of monthly subscription revenue from Udemy Business customers as the instructor revenue pool. Each instructor\'s share of this amount is equal to their share of the total minutes consumed across all Udemy Business courses. For example, if 3% of all consumption in Udemy Business courses for a given month occurred in your courses, you\'d receive 3% of the Udemy Business instructor revenue pool for that month.  </string>
    <string name="membership_site">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020A membership site is any part of your online business that contains gated content (information behind a paywall). A gate is simply a barrier to limit access to your content to those who pay or you decide to let in. Once inside, they get access to your member area with exclusive content and privileges.
                                                                 \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020It\'s not a new business, in fact, its been online for over 17 years, but what is new is their \'rate of growth\' that\'s being driven by the evolution of the Internet as it\'s maturing.
       \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020They\'re estimated to be doing about $200 Million per year in sales from what is essentially a $25 per month online membership site full of \"how-to\" videos and tutorials.

</string>
    <string name="kindle_ebook">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Over the lifetime of a book?
      \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Anywhere from nothing to millions. Average? Less than $100. The problem is the average bit. There are some 50 million books on Kindle. Around 15 million of them have a sales rank, meaning they did in fact sell enough to get a rank.
        \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020For Kindle books priced from $0.99 to $2.98, you receive a 35% royalty on each sale. For Kindle books priced from $2.99 to $9.99, you receive a 70% royalty on each sale. For Kindle books priced above $9.99, you receive a 35% royalty on each sale.
</string>
    <string name="affiliate_marketing">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020In an affiliate marketing program, you earn income by promoting other people’s products and services
                                                   \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020 Here are some stats on the average income of affiliate marketers. According to PayScale, average annual affiliate marketing passive income is $51,217. The bottom 10% of affiliate marketers earn $37,000, and the top 10% earn $71,000.
                                                   \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020 Glassdoor‘s affiliate marketing income           statistics put potential earnings even higher. Average annual earnings for affiliate marketers are $65,800, with the range between $42,000 at the low end, and $83,000 at the top end.
</string>
    <string name="blogging">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020In India, a professional blogger can earn up to $10,000 every month. On average, a blogger can earn between $300 and $400 per month. Celebrity bloggers can earn in the range of $20,000 to $30,000 every month. Blogging has emerged as a serious profession for many people in India over the last few years. But how easy is it to make money from blogging in India?
        \n\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Some of the professional bloggers earn even more than the annual income of employees at the executive level. Today, blogging is growing at a fast pace and is being regarded as a mainstream profession. So, if you want to know how to make money from blogging in India, you have come to the right place. Here are the top 15 ways to make money from blogging in India.
</string>
    <string name="privacy">      By clicking you are Agreeing to  <font fgcolor="#30A6A6">Privacy Policy</font>\n                            and <font fgcolor="#30A6A6">Terms &amp; Conditions</font></string>
</resources>